animetake.tv 2016-01-23

# Privacy Policy | Animetake

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us info@animetake.tv At animetake.tv, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by animetake.tv and how it is used. Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

* * *

**© Animetake.tv 2015**  
Copyrights and trademarks for the anime, and other promotional materials are held by their respective owners and their use is allowed under the fair use clause of the Copyright Law.
